

# YADDY KATHERIN ROJAS SANTOS

**4** (+57) 318-727-6844

yaddyrojasantos@hotmail.com

Bucaramanga, Santander, Colombia

https://www.linkedin.com/in/yaddy-katherin-rojas-santos-657171149/

## **LANGUAGES**

**English:** Intermediate

Spanish: Native

## **SKILLS**

Programming languages include HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Angular, TypeScript, NodeJS, .NET CORE, C#, JavaScript, Visual Basic, JQuery, SQL server, PL/SQL Oracle, and others.

#### **SKILLSET**

- Agile Methods (SCRUM)
- Teamwork
- Leadership
- Problem solving
- Willingness to learn
- Collaboration
- Active Listening
- Conversational English

## **SOFTWARE ENGINEER**

Developer Full Stack with experience in create and maintain web application and desktop application, team working and leadership of projects. I characterize me to be a person responsible, honest, on time, with a sense of belonging, ability to solve problems, and open to learning new skills.

## **EXPERIENCE**

#### SOFTWARE ENGINEER CORE

Oct 2020 - Jul 2022

Sistemas y computadores S.A - Component Innovation Engineer

- Develop Full-Stack web applications using ASP.NET, web API, C#, LINQ, JavaScript, jQuery, CSS, HTML, SQL Server, Bootstrap, and others.
- Basic kowledge of the tool Azure Devops and agile methods Scrum.
- Maintain desktop applications using ASP.NET core, Visual Basic, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, jQuery, PL/SQL (oracle) and others.
- Information gathering, flowchart design, layout, and views, leadership development the project.
- Train new employees and leadership of projects.

### **SOFTWARE DEVELOPER**

Jul - Ago 2021

 Maintain web applications for a hotel using Framework Angular 11, CSS, Express, NodeJS, Typescript and GitHub. (https://casacampestrelacosecha.com/)

# **GRADUATION PROJECT - UIS**

Jul 2019 - Jul 2020

University Degree in System Engineer

- Maintain desktop applications using Delphi 7.
- Develop Full-Stack web applications using framework and tool like Angular, TypeScript, Spring Boot, MySQL, NodeJS. Where the user must fill out a form with data based on the Framingham heart study, a graph is generated showing the tendency of pre-hypertensive patients who suffer from AHT

#### SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Ago 2017 - Dec 2017

 Maintain web application for a tourism business using Joomla Content Management System (CMS) (<a href="http://santostours.co/">http://santostours.co/</a>)

Jan 2018 – May 2018

 Design and develop a web page application for a hotel with content specific about tourism in this town using frameworks like HTML5, PHP, JavaScript, Materialize. (https://casacampestrelacosecha.com/)

## **EDUCATION**

## **BACHELOR'S DEGREE - 2020**

Systems and informatic Engineering Universidad Industrial de Santander (UIS)

#### HIGH SCHOOL - 2011

Instituto Técnico Nacional de Comercio Bucaramanga